<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature
      id="com.jhappy.wbutil.feature"
      label="JHappy Windowbuilder Util Feature"
      version="0.0.1.qualifier"
      provider-name="JHAPPY">

   <description>
      Description:
This plugin provides a utility to automatically align Non-Visual
Beans within the WindowBuilder editor. It extracts beans marked
with the &quot;@wbp.nonvisual&quot; tag and rearranges their layout coordinates
based on customizable preferences. Users can define the starting
position, spacing, and wrapping rows, as well as sort beans by
field name or class type. This tool ensures a clean and organized
design environment by preventing overlapping icons in the graphical
editor.
説明:
このプラグインは、WindowBuilderエディタ内の「Non-Visual Bean」を自動的に整列させるユーティリティを提供します
。ソースコード内の &quot;@wbp.nonvisual&quot; タグが付与された要素を抽出し、設定画面で指定した座標や間隔に基づいてレイアウトを再配置します
。開始座標、間隔、折り返し行数の設定に加えて、変数名順またはクラス型順でのソートが可能です 。グラフィカルエディタ上でのアイコンの重なりを防ぎ、設計環境をクリーンに保ちます
。
说明:
此插件提供了一个用于在 WindowBuilder 编辑器中自动整列“非可视化 Bean (Non-Visual Beans)”的实用工具
。它能够提取带有 &quot;@wbp.nonvisual&quot; 标签的组件，并根据用户自定义的参数重新排列其布局坐标 。用户可以设置起始坐标、间距和换行行数，并支持按变量名或类类型进行排序
。该工具通过防止图形编辑器中的图标重叠，确保设计环境的整洁有序



Icon Credits:
The icon icons/ChooseComponent.gif is sourced from the official Eclipse WindowBuilder repository.
   </description>

   <copyright>
      Copyright (c) 2026 JHappy
   </copyright>

   <license url="http://www.example.com/license">
      MIT License

Copyright (c) 2026 JHappy

Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy
of this software and associated documentation files (the &quot;Software&quot;), to deal
in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights
to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell
copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is
furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:

The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in all
copies or substantial portions of the Software.

THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED &quot;AS IS&quot;, WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR
IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY,
FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE
AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER
LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM,
OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE
SOFTWARE.
   </license>

   <plugin
         id="com.jhappy.wbutil"
         version="0.0.0"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.jhappy.wbutil.nl_ja"
         version="0.0.0"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.jhappy.wbutil.nl_zh"
         version="0.0.0"/>

</feature>
